<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<articles xmlns="http://www.uts.edu.au/31284/wsd-diary"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.uts.edu.au/31284/wsd-diary articles.xsd">

<!-- Article data including id, title, published date, author ID, full text and category tag -->

	<article>
		<id>7</id>
		<title>Hazy morning for Sydney as smoke hangs over city</title>
		<publishedDate>2014-05-22+10:00</publishedDate>
		<authorId>2</authorId>
		<fullText>Sydneysiders awoke to a red dawn this morning as the city
			was swamped by smoke caused by fog and several hazard reduction
			burns.
			The NSW Rural Fire Service said the hazy pall was a result of a number
			of burns they have conducted in the greater Sydney area over the past
			week.
			People with asthma or lung conditions were advised to stay indoors due to
			the high smoke.
			The NSW RFS said the smoke would start dissipating by mid-morning and
			was expected to clear by lunch time.
			Hazard reduction burns have been taking place in Ku-ring-gai, the
			Hawkesbury and the Blue Mountains over the past few days.
			
			
			Read more:
			http://www.smh.com.au/nsw/hazy-morning-for-sydney-as-smoke-hangs-over-city-20140522-zrkje.html#ixzz32OzsnvPE
		</fullText>
		<categoryTag>News</categoryTag>
		<authorOnly>false</authorOnly>
	</article>
	<article>
		<id>8</id>
		<title>Call to halt 'white elephant' bridge across Anzac Parade
		</title>
		<publishedDate>2014-05-22+10:00</publishedDate>
		<authorId>2</authorId>
		<fullText>Support is crumbling for a $25 million bridge across Anzac
			Parade near Sydney Cricket Ground, with transport lobby groups and
			the City of Sydney calling for an urgent halt to
			construction.
			The government is attempting to get the bridge built in time for the
			2015 Cricket World Cup, and this week said building work had started
			on the project. But plans for the bridge continue to draw the ire of
			locals and people who might be expected to use it, and key backers
			the government had been relying on are pulling away.
			One of the main complaints about the bridge is that it is not being
			built where people want to walk. The majority of people who walk
			between Central Station and the SCG cross Anzac Parade at Fitzroy
			Street, one block away from where the bridge is planned.
			Roads and Maritime Services says it will use signs to direct
			pedestrians to the bridge.
			Another complaint about the bridge, to be named after former test cricketer
			Albert ''Tibby'' Cotter, is that it will not connect to the cycleway
			on Anzac Parade.
			In promoting the bridge plan in April, Roads and Maritime Services
			said: ''Bicycle NSW and the City of Sydney have been consulted and
			are supportive of the plan.''
			Both organisations want construction suspended.
			''It needs further review,'' said Sophie Bartho, communications director
			at Bicycle NSW. ''The fact that the bridge and the existing cycle
			path are not directly connected is a major concern.''
			Lord mayor Clover Moore has written to the government requesting it call
			a halt to work on the bridge, which risked becoming ''an expensive
			white elephant''.
			''I was shocked to find Roads and Maritime Services approved the
			proposed bridge on May 14 with two minor design changes,'' Cr Moore
			said. ''Just days later early work has begun, blocking off a large
			section of parkland.''
			On Monday Roads Minister Duncan Gay, Sports Minister Stuart Ayres and
			chairman of the SCG Trust Tony Shepherd announced the start of work
			on the project. The SCG Trust partly supports the project so it can
			use the western side of Moore Park for car parking. The bridge would
			allow people who have parked on Moore Park to cross easily to the
			SCG.
			Speaking in Parliament, Mr Gay said ''everyone likes'' the bridge. ''It has a
			good name, it is a great design and it is in the right
			place.''
			The bridge is also opposed by the Paddington Society, Action for Public
			Transport, the Centennial Park Residents Association and
			BikeSydney.
			A spokeswoman for Mr Gay said the government had already signed
			contracts for early building works on the project.
			
			
			Read more:
			http://www.smh.com.au/nsw/call-to-halt-white-elephant-bridge-across-anzac-parade-20140521-38p40.html#ixzz32P0HMc7Y
		</fullText>
		<categoryTag>News</categoryTag>
		<authorOnly>false</authorOnly>
	</article>
	<article>
		<id>9</id>
		<title>Michael Rogers wins stage, Cadel Evans still leads Giro
			d'Italia</title>
		<publishedDate>2014-05-20+10:00</publishedDate>
		<authorId>2</authorId>
		<fullText>Australia's Michael Rogers has won the 11th stage of the
			Giro d'Italia as his compatriot Cadel Evans retained the leader's
			pink jersey.
			Rogers, riding for the Tinkoff team, came home 10 seconds ahead of the pack
			at the end of the 249km ride from Collecchio to Savona after breaking
			clear on the final descent, 20km from the finish.
			Simon Geschke of Germany claimed second place in front of Italy's Enrico
			Battaglin and Wilco Kelderman of the Netherlands.
			
			
			For the 34-year-old Rogers, it was a first stage win in a Grand Tour and
			his first success since his return to the sport following a positive
			test for clenbuterol last year.
			Rogers had always claimed that his positive test was due to eating
			contaminated food and he was later cleared to return to racing by the
			International Cycling Union (UCI) in time to compete in the
			Liege-Bastogne-Liege classic in April.
			"It was one of the hardest rides of my life, for sure," he
			said.
			"At the top of the climb, I realised that most guys in the group were GC
			contenders and this was the time to jump. So I went. From then on, it
			was all about keeping my head down, pedalling away and I guess I was
			a little lucky that the GC guys were probably looking at each other,
			hesitating a bit."
			The victory for Rogers, who dedicated it to his Italian wife, continues
			Australia's fine record in this year's Giro.
			The Orica-GreenEdge team won the opening stage team time trial and
			Michael Matthews triumphed on the sixth stage, while Matthews held
			the pink jersey from the second stage until it was seized by Evans
			after stage eight.
			Evans, of the BMC team, will now hope to extend his lead of 57 seconds down
			to Colombia's Rigoberto Uran in Thursday's 12th stage, a 41.9km
			individual time trial from Barbaresco to Barolo.
			"The time trial is always the race of truth," Evans said. "We have had a
			difficult first week.
			"Now we have also had a very long and intense stage. I think that will
			probably have a little bit of an effect on the
			performances.
			"For me, it is one of the key stages and on paper, it looks like it suits
			me. I go into it feeling pretty well, feeling ok."
			There were several falls on Wednesday's stage, and Germany's Fabian
			Wegmann was forced to abandon the race along with Australian Luke
			Durbridge.
			Former leader Matthews pulled out of the race at the start of the day due
			to injury.
			
			
			Read more:
			http://www.smh.com.au/sport/cycling/michael-rogers-wins-stage-cadel-evans-still-leads-giro-ditalia-20140522-zrkjf.html#ixzz32P0qWUBN
		</fullText>
		<categoryTag>Sport</categoryTag>
		<authorOnly>false</authorOnly>
	</article>
	<article>
		<id>10</id>
		<title>Jedinak to set the tone for success as Socceroos captain
		</title>
		<publishedDate>2014-04-28+10:00</publishedDate>
		<authorId>1</authorId>
		<fullText>Socceroos midfielder Mile Jedinak has promised to “lead by
			example” at next month’s World Cup after being appointed
			Australian captain on Wednesday.
			Jedinak joins one of Australian football's most exclusive clubs, becoming
			only the fourth man to lead the Socceroos to the global showpiece,
			joining Peter Wilson (1974), Mark Viduka (2006) and Lucas Neill
			(2010).
			The 29-year-old has enjoyed a meteoric rise to fame in recent years,
			crowned by an exceptional season with Crystal Palace - the club he
			captained to promotion last season and then again in the English
			Premier League in the campaign just finished.
			Jedinak said he wanted to bring his leadership qualities honed at Selhurst
			Park to the Socceroos as they front three of the best teams in Brazil
			in the group stages: Chile, The Netherlands and Spain.
			“It’s probably the biggest honour I’ll receive so I’m really
			looking forward to the challenge ahead,” he said. “I tend to lead
			by example. It’s what I know, it’s what I do [and] you might
			alter and be a bit more vocal than at other times. I always try to
			set an example, not just for inexperienced members but for everybody,
			by how I conduct myself.”
			Jedinak will be joined by two vice-captains, Tim Cahill and Mark Bresciano,
			who will each be competing in their third and final World Cup.
			Jedinak, with 43 caps to his name, will be going to his second,
			although his last experience was not so positive - playing only in
			the Socceroos' 4-0 thumping at the hands of Germany four years
			ago.
			Socceroos boss Ange Postecoglou hailed Jedinak’s “unbelievable” club
			season as the major reason he was given the nod.
			“He’s led from the front, he’s led a group of players in a team in the
			English Premier League which many had written off,” he said. “A
			lot of those characteristics apply to us right now. I know that when
			we get to Brazil and face up to the challenges we need to face up to,
			Mile and Timmy and Mark will be leading from the front.”
			Postecoglou hailed the location of the announcement - Terrigal on the
			Central Coast - as fitting given it was where Jedinak began his
			A-League career, famously, on a short-term contract with the Mariners
			in 2006. He then left for Turkey in 2009 before making his big move
			to England in 2011.
			“It’s quite significant we’re making this announcement in this city
			because five years ago this is the place where Mile put his head down
			and, with a determined attitude, he began climbing the football
			ladder,” Postecoglou said. “And in the past 12 months, I think we
			still significantly underplay what a year he’s had in one of the
			toughest leagues in the world. In my mind, he’s probably been one
			of the top five Australian sportsmen in the past 12 months with what
			he’s achieved.”
			Bresciano said he, Jedinak and Cahill “would try to lead the team all
			together”.
			“We’ll try to bring our experience into the team and support the younger
			boys,” he said. “They’ve been doing very well. Now our main
			task is to get there, prepare as best we can and help them settle
			into a World Cup.”
			While Jedinak first captained the Socceroos in their most recent friendly,
			a 4-3 loss against Ecuador, he is in doubt to play in the match
			against South Africa in Sydney next Monday. He injured himself in the
			last match of the season for Palace three weeks ago, coming off in
			the 59th minute - the only minutes he’s missed all
			season.
			“Whether or not Monday is too early remains to be seen but I’ll try to give
			myself every opportunity,” he said. “It [the groin strain] is
			coming along really well.”
			Despite Australia’s near-impossible group in Brazil, Jedinak admitted
			he’d even indulged a few visions about the unthinkable since being
			told he would be the national captain.
			“Yeah, I’ve had dreams about holding the [World] Cup,” he said.
			“I’d be sitting here lying if I said I hadn’t. But it’s so
			far away now, your focus isn’t even game by game, it’s day by day
			and how we’re going to work towards that goal.”
			
			
			Read more:
			http://www.smh.com.au/fifa-world-cup-2014/australia-2014/jedinak-to-set-the-tone-for-success-as-socceroos-captain-20140521-zrk5a.html#ixzz32P1KVzx2
		</fullText>
		<categoryTag>Sport</categoryTag>
		<authorOnly>false</authorOnly>
	</article>
	<article>
		<id>11</id>
		<title>Batman v Superman movie's full name revealed</title>
		<publishedDate>2014-05-01+10:00</publishedDate>
		<authorId>1</authorId>
		<fullText>The highly anticipated Batman versus Superman film has
			finally been given a title.
			It will be Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice.
			The title is the first solid indication that DC Comics, the comic book
			franchise owned by Warner Bros, is mounting a fight back against the
			cinema dominance of its longtime rival Marvel.
			Despite a longer history with individual franchises for Batman and Superman,
			DC Comics has been eclipsed in the last decade in the movie business
			by Marvel-owned properties, such as Spiderman, Thor and
			Iron-Man.
			Marvel has also successfully built a multi-character franchise in The
			Avengers, as well as a TV spin-off, Marvel: Agents of
			S.H.I.E.L.D.
			At the same time, other DC-owned hero franchises such as Aquaman,
			Wonder Woman and Green Lantern have foundered in TV and film
			development hell, or failed as pilots.
			As well, a planned Justice League movie, which would have starred
			Australian model Megan Gale as Wonder Woman, never made it into
			production.
			The title of the Batman-Superman film - Dawn of Justice - is a nod to
			the Justice League, DC's iconic gathering of superheros.
			In comic books and animated TV iterations, the Justice League has
			included Superman, Batman (and sometimes Robin), Wonder Woman,
			Aquaman, Green Lantern and The Flash.
			The upcoming film, a sequel to the Superman solo film Man of Steel, will
			star Henry Cavill as Superman and Ben Affleck as Batman. Filming is
			due to take place in Africa and the South Pacific.
			Fans got an early hint that it would introduce other members of the
			Justice League with confirmation some time ago that Israel
			actress/model Gal Gadot would also star in the film as Wonder
			Woman.
			The presence of other characters from DC Comics lore - such as Batman's
			butler Alfred (Jeremy Irons) and Superman's nemesis Lex Luthor (Jesse
			Eisenberg) - suggest director Zack Snyder plans to heavily mine the
			comic book histories of the characters.
			It is expected that Snyder will follow Batman v Superman with a
			fully-fledged Justice League film.
			Batman v Superman is due in cinemas globally in May, 2016.
			
			
			Read more:
			http://www.smh.com.au/entertainment/movies/batman-v-superman-movies-full-name-revealed-20140522-zrkkq.html#ixzz32P1YpqgE
		</fullText>
		<categoryTag>Entertainment</categoryTag>
		<authorOnly>false</authorOnly>
	</article>
	<article>
		<id>12</id>
		<title>Game of Thrones recap: Tyrion Lannister struggles to find a
			champion fighter to save him</title>
		<publishedDate>2014-05-21+10:00</publishedDate>
		<authorId>1</authorId>
		<fullText>Hello, Throners.
			
			I see you’ve entered my personal Game of Thrones recap room through
			the unguarded window. Well, then. I’m going to pour a glass of
			wine, replace it with a slurpee because I’m not actually into wine,
			and then I’m going to let you do what you do best.
			
			Take off your clothes.
			
			Oh yes, Throners. I’m in control here, and I’m going to be doing a
			lot of staring at your firm, supple physiques. What’s that you say?
			Inappropriate in a recap? That’s probably true. I’m valuing your
			worth based solely on your appearance. I’m treating you like
			incredibly buff meat. Frankly, it’s offensive. But you know,
			Throners, I’m still seeing clothes covering your well-chiselled
			obliques and gently sloping glutes.
			
			Now, that’s better. Pass me my smelling salts.
			
			If you are genuinely upset by sexual harassment in online pop culture
			blog form, remember my introductions often reflect my theme, which
			this week is “jokes and lies”.
			
			So you see, I’m only joking about you needing to remove your clothes
			to read on. It's up to you how seriously you take that joke...
			
			
			But back on track. There is a housekeeping matter to attend to regarding
			upcoming recaps as well, so if you do make it to end, please have a
			look and leave a comment if you can.
			
			In the meantime, let’s kick over some snowcastles and get slappy with
			another Raven On Game of Thrones recap.
			
			Reminder: spoilers will be included below, so only read on if you’ve seen
			the episode. We’re discovering the storyline through the TV series
			(reading the books after each has finished), so no dropping important
			future plot points in the comments, or we’ll give you what they
			refer to in the Vale as an “extreme mooning”).
			
			Read more:
			http://www.smh.com.au/entertainment/tv-and-radio/game-of-thrones-recap-tyrion-lannister-struggles-to-find-a-champion-fighter-to-save-him-20140520-zrhyq.html#ixzz32P1r2Nnb
		</fullText>
		<categoryTag>Entertainment</categoryTag>
		<authorOnly>false</authorOnly>
	</article>
	<article>
		<id>13</id>
		<title>Google chooses to spend income its own way</title>
		<publishedDate>2014-05-15+10:00</publishedDate>
		<authorId>1</authorId>
		<fullText>Google was keeping a large portion of its cash outside the
			US so it could use as much as $US30 billion for possible
			acquisitions, the company said in a letter to regulators.
			The web search engine owner generates about half its revenue outside
			the US and avoids paying US taxes by keeping foreign earnings abroad.
			Google needs the cash for deals as competition increases outside the
			US, according to a December 20 letter to the US Securities and
			Exchange Commission, filed this week as part of a correspondence with
			the agency regarding disclosures.
			''We continue to expect substantial use of our offshore earnings for
			acquisitions as our global business has expanded into other product
			offerings like mobile devices,'' the letter says. ''It is reasonable
			to forecast that Google needs between $US20-30 billion of foreign
			earnings to fund potential acquisitions of foreign targets and
			foreign technology rights from US targets in 2013 and
			beyond.''
			Google, while facing criticism for keeping the cash parked overseas, has
			been stepping up its deal activity, including the $US3.2 billion
			purchase earlier this year of digital-thermostat maker Nest Labs,
			based in Palo Alto, California.
			The company also has made several smaller purchases, benefiting Google's
			advertising, cloud services and mobile businesses.
			''In the past few years we have completed significant acquisitions with
			the individual deal size increasing in more recent years, and this
			trend is likely to continue in future years,'' Google said in the
			letter, which was a response to a question from the SEC about its
			plans for reinvesting foreign earnings.
			At the end of last year, Google held $US33.6 billion of its $US58.7
			billion of cash, cash equivalents and marketable securities in its
			foreign subsidiaries.
			''If these funds are needed for our operations in the US, we would be
			required to accrue and pay US taxes to repatriate these funds,'' the
			company said in a filing in February. ''However, our intent is to
			permanently reinvest these funds outside of the US and our current
			plans do not demonstrate a need to repatriate them to fund our US
			operations.''
			The company also sees other uses for earnings made outside the US, such
			as $US2-4 billion for capital expenditures. That includes data
			centres and other operations. The company also needs $US12-14 billion
			for a research-and-development cost-sharing agreement.
			The filing was part of an exchange between the SEC and Google that began
			last year related to questions about disclosures in the company's
			2012 annual report.
			
			
			Read more:
			http://www.smh.com.au/business/google-chooses-to-spend-income-its-own-way-20140521-38p0t.html#ixzz32P2FkjVu
		</fullText>
		<categoryTag>Business</categoryTag>
		<authorOnly>false</authorOnly>
	</article>
	<article>
		<id>14</id>
		<title>Aussie bank brands trump Twitter and eBay</title>
		<publishedDate>2014-05-22+10:00</publishedDate>
		<authorId>1</authorId>
		<fullText>The brands of two of Australia's big banks are more valuable
			than those of oil giant Shell or household tech names Twitter, eBay
			and Linkedin, according to a global market research agency.
			Commonwealth Bank and ANZ made Millward Brown's Top 100 Brandz report
			for 2014, ranked 44 and 51 respectively.
			The pair, two of four Australian companies on the list, also beat
			international brands Gillette (52), FedEx (58), Swedish fashion
			retailer H&amp;M (63) and Gucci (60).
			Senior business consultant at Millward Brown Australia Johnny Panagiotidis
			said Commonwealth Bank had moved up four places on 2013, with an 18
			per cent rise in brand value to $US21 billion ($22.76 billion) this
			year.
			Westpac also made the list with an impressive 17 per cent rise in brand
			value to $US12 billion, which pushed it up three places to No.
			85.
			''The impressive growth in brand value of the two Australian brands in
			this year's Top 100 is in line with the strong recovery in valuations
			seen across the globe," Mr Panagiotidis said.
			ANZ's ranking was unchanged, despite its brand value jumping 15 per cent
			to $US19 billion.
			Overall, the brand value of companies has bounced back strongly since the
			financial crisis, Mr Panagiotidis said.
			The combined value of the top 100 has nearly doubled since the first
			ranking was produced in 2006 to $US2.9 trillion.
			This is an increase of 49 per cent compared with the 2008 valuation,
			which marked the start of the banking and currency crisis.
			''The global financial crisis was a challenging time for many
			companies but despite fluctuating macro-economic conditions and the
			impact of digital disruption, we still see seventy-one of the brands
			listed in our 2014 Top 100 that were there in 2008,'' Mr Panagiotidis
			said.
			''Strong brands are better able to weather the storm and, when valued by
			companies, create value for them."
			Dominant supermarket group Woolworths was also on the list, after falling two
			places to No.82.
			US search engine Google topple rival technology behemoth Apple, which
			spent the past three year's as the world's most valuable
			brand.
			Google's brand value shot up 40 per cent in a year to $US158.84 billion,
			Millward Brown said, thanks to its internet-linked eyewear Google
			Glass.
			The company has joined hands with Luxottica, which owns Ray-Ban and
			other high-end brands, to sell the new product in the United
			States.
			"Google has been hugely innovative in the last year with Google Glass,
			investments in artificial intelligence and a multitude of
			partnerships that see its Android operating system becoming embedded
			in other goods such as cars,'' said Nick Cooper, Managing Director of
			Millward Brown Optimor.
			''All of this activity sends a very strong signal to consumers about what
			Google is about and it has coincided with a slowdown at
			Apple."
			Technology companies continued to dominate the list, with IBM and Microsoft
			rounding out the top four.
			Millward Brown said the sector, which accounted for 29 per cent of the list,
			also included many of the list's fastest climbers. Leading Chinese
			internet brand Tencent scored the biggest increase, leaping 97 per
			cent to $US54 billion ($A58.53 billion), catapulting it to No.
			14.
			This was followed by Facebook, which rose 68 per cent to $US36 billion to
			take No. 21 spot.
			
			
			Read more:
			http://www.smh.com.au/business/media-and-marketing/aussie-bank-brands-trump-twitter-and-ebay-20140521-38noq.html#ixzz32P2OMAO2
		</fullText>
		<categoryTag>Business</categoryTag>
		<authorOnly>false</authorOnly>
	</article>
	<article>
		<id>15</id>
		<title>Apple sued over vanishing text messages after iPhones swapped
			for Androids</title>
		<publishedDate>2014-05-20+10:00</publishedDate>
		<authorId>2</authorId>
		<fullText>A former iPhone user is suing Apple, claiming the company's
			messaging system interfered with delivery of texts after she switched
			to an Android smartphone.
			
			Apple's iMessage retains text messages sent from other users of Apple
			devices and won't deliver them to her Samsung phone running on
			Google's Android operating system, Adrienne Moore said in the
			complaint filed last week in San Jose, California.
			
			People who replace their Apple devices with non-Apple smartphones and
			tablets are "penalised and unable to obtain the full benefits of
			their wireless-service contracts", according to the
			complaint.
			
			Apple has battled smartphone manufacturers in court, most recently in a
			patent lawsuit against Samsung in San Jose. Apple accused Samsung of
			infringement based in large part on its use of Android-based
			features.
			
			Advertisement
			Google, meanwhile, is pushing for a bigger piece of the smartphone market
			with new features and updates to attract more users. The efforts
			helped the search-engine company claim more than 75 per cent of the
			smartphone industry at the end of last year, according to
			Gartner.
			
			Apple and Google last week declared a cease-fire in their
			intellectual-property wars, saying they will work together in some
			areas of patent reform.
			
			The text-messaging lawsuit, which seeks class-action status and
			undetermined damages, claims Apple failed to disclose that switching
			to a device other than one running on Apple's iOS operating system
			would result in the interference. The suit is based on contractual
			interference and unfair competition laws.
			
			Apple spokeswoman Kristin Huguet declined to comment on the
			lawsuit.
			
			Read more:
			http://www.smh.com.au/digital-life/mobiles/apple-sued-over-vanishing-text-messages-after-iphones-swapped-for-androids-20140520-zri7i.html
		</fullText>
		<categoryTag>Technology</categoryTag>
		<authorOnly>false</authorOnly>
	</article>
	<article>
		<id>16</id>
		<title>Mario Golf World Tour game review</title>
		<publishedDate>2014-05-22+10:00</publishedDate>
		<authorId>2</authorId>
		<fullText>Mario has repeatedly proven himself as the world's most
			versatile athlete, but it's been a decade since the tubby plumber
			last hit the links. Fortunately, he still knows how to play a great
			game.
			
			World Tour lets you play three traditional golf courses as your customised
			Mii character, trying to lower your handicap and win the trio of
			"Castle Club" tournaments. It's a good training ground to learn how
			to hit the ball consistently, add spin and account for the breeze,
			but the conservative holes soon become dull and the campaign can be
			polished off in just a few hours.
			
			It's the six wacky nine-hole Mario World courses that make the game
			special and will keep you coming back. There's a course set at
			Bowser's Castle that includes exploding bombs and even an underwater
			setting. 
			
			Advertisement
			You can belt your ball into pipes and dash pads to gain extra metres,
			and hit Mario Kart's famous item boxes to earn single-use power-ups.
			Special shots include the Bullet Bill, which fires deadly straight
			regardless of the wind, and the Fire Flower, which can burn a pathway
			through trees.
			
			Controls are simple to learn but you always have tricky decisions to make,
			with big rewards for pulling off risky shots but disastrous
			consequences for mistimed misadventures.
			
			New courses, characters and costumes are unlocked via the puzzle-like
			challenges, which set you fun tasks such as hitting the ball through
			deviously placed rings, collecting scattered coins, duels against
			other champs or races against the clock.
			
			There are official online tournaments or you can host your own and choose
			custom rules.
			
			Players can also buy six more downloadable 18-hole courses which come with
			bonus characters, but the price might grate considering the anaemic
			Castle Club campaign.
			
			Fortunately, even if you don't spend more cash you will still find World Tour
			challenging and rewarding. 
			
			Read more:
			http://www.smh.com.au/digital-life/games/mario-golf-world-tour-game-review-20140517-zrbdn.html
		</fullText>
		<categoryTag>Technology</categoryTag>
		<authorOnly>false</authorOnly>
	</article>
</articles>
